# （脑瓜崩）
(Forehead Flicker)
# 朋友之间，有的时候为了增进友谊
To improve our friendship between buddies
# 经常会开一些善意的小玩笑
We mess up with each other all the time
# 躲在门后，吓对方一跳啊
Like hiding behind the door and scaring them
# 做一些小恶作剧啊
Some pranks
# 弹个脑瓜崩之类的
Like flicking them on the forehead
# 但是有的朋友，因为说身体素质的原因
But some guys have limitations on physical strength
# 中指没有力量，没有办法弹出一个响亮清脆悦耳的脑瓜崩儿
Their fingers are too weak to make a loud, crisp and sweet flick on the forehead
# 所以说，我做了一个脑瓜崩辅助器
Thus, I made a flicking assistant device
# 可以看一下，有弹簧
Have a look, there’s a spring inside
# 带起来也非常方便
It’s easy to wear too
# 把中指插进去就可以，后面有根手镯
Put your middle finger in. There’s a bracelet too
# 安装上
Just assemble it
# 就可以了
That’s it
# 看一下，力量如何
Let’s see how strong it is
# 先拿鸡蛋做个实验
Let’s test it with an egg first
# （暖壶鱼缸）
(Thermos Bottle Fish Tank)
# （暖气椅）
(Heater Bench)
# 天气越来越冷，每天我工作完
It’s getting colder and colder. Every day I got off work,
# 都喜欢靠在这个暖气片旁边暖和一下
I’d like to lean on this heating radiator
# 但是蹲时间久了发现腿比较麻
But my legs went numb after a while
# 所以说我准备做一个暖气春秋椅
So I planned to make a heater bench
# 差不多已经制作完成了
Almost done
# 本想油完漆再安装，但是说我已经迫不及待了
I was going to paint it and then install it. But I can no longer wait
# 先坐上再说吧
Let’s have a try first
# 看它的温度
Let’s measure the temperature
# 坐一下试试效果
Let’s sit on it and see
# 哇
Whoa
# 暖和！
So warm!
# 这温度是四周围把你包起来的
The heat surrounds you, it embraces you
# 臀部后背都能感觉到
You can feel it in your hip and your back
# 而且
And
# 而且这种椅子不仅
And the bench is not only
# 冬天坐着比较暖和
Warm during winter
# 夏天坐着也比较凉爽
It’s also cool during summer
# 一年四季都能用，谢谢
Good all year round. Thanks